Affan Naim

C6, Suroor Apartment, Sir Syed Nagar, Aligarh. 202002

affan123naim@gmail.com

+91-9528662147

Profile

Expert business strategist with a sound understanding of organizational development and sales. Skilled communicator with 1 year of experience providing company with successful solutions to building organizational success. Persuasive negotiator who uses integrity and professionalism in presenting joint ventures, assessing acquisition opportunities and identifying new markets. Innovative thinker who detects more efficient ways of growing company assets by recommending new products, revolutionizing current product offerings and testing new market opportunities.

Skills

- 1 year of experience in Ed-Tech Inside Sales/telesales experience in a B2C environment with excellent communication skills, enthusiastic gogetter and willing to meet targets.
- Having a keen interest and deep understanding of the Indian education sector.
- Have a knack for sales.
- Good verbal and written communication skills.
- Good interpersonal and presentation skills.
- Fluent in English & Hindi.
- Business Development.
- Corporate Sales.
- Direct Sales.
- Sales.
- Telecalling

Education

B.Tech - Mechanical

Aligarh Muslim University, Aligarh Apr 2021 - Apr 2024

Sayyed Hamid Senior Secondary School, AMU, Aligarh PCM Senior Secondary

Our Lady of Fatima, Aligarh High school

Apr 2016 - Apr 2018

Apr 2018 - Aug 2020

Professional Experience

Vocal Code

Business Development Executive April 2022 - March 2023

Neokinetic

Lead Generation Executive March 2023 - currently working